<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:10:57 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This is post 4</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:10:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post4/</guid>
      <description>content of post 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So You Have To Work From Home</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 09:57:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post3/</guid>
      <description>The novel coronavirus has, as of Friday, infected more than 100,000 people and killed more than 3,400 globally. Fear, uncertainty, and doubt are pervasive. What happens next is anyone’s guess, but it’s safe to assume that whatever it is will be a shitshow of historic magnitude—it’s already a tragedy for thousands of families and a lesson in the fragility of our globalized world.
Most of us, so far at least, are experiencing this ballooning catastrophe in the low-hum vibration that precedes any potential impending doom—the kind of energy buzz you get before a big storm hits mixed with the odd, dull nothingness of waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Coronavirus FAQs, Answered: Wearing Masks, Canceling Air Travel, and More</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 15:10:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post2/</guid>
      <description>The ongoing outbreak of a newly discovered, sometimes fatal coronavirus has many people wondering how much they should be altering their daily lives to avoid infection. As the disease known as COVID-19 has begun spreading locally in parts of the U.S., we’ve compiled answers to commonly asked questions submitted by our readers, friends, and coworkers.
Q: How long can the virus survive on surfaces? Do disinfectant sprays and wipes work against it?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>